A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers FA108
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates Files, 1942-1977 1962-1977; 2; 17.5 Cubic Feet 51 Boxes
  - Addresses - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, December 2, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Addresses - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, December 8, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Addresses - Princeton University - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, December 1, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Addresses - Protestant Council of the City of New York, October 23, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Addresses - Protestant Council of the City of New York, October 23, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Addresses - Ramon Magsaysay Center (Manila) Dedication, September 2, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Addresses - Riverside Church, November 6, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Addresses - Rockefeller Foundation Symposium, April 2, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Addresses - Senate Subcommittee on Labor - Health, Education, and Welfare, April 9, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Addresses - "Speaking Freely" (TV Program), June 24, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Addresses - Spelman College, April 1964 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Addresses - Stanford University, May 26, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Addresses - United Nations Association of the United States of America, May 23, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - 1969 May 23 (Box P 171, Folder 11)
  - Addresses - United Nations Development Decade Conference, May 9, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - U.N. World Population Conference (Box P 171, Folder 12)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Addresses - United Nations World Population Conference - Working Papers, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Addresses - University of Arkansas, May 2, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Addresses - University of Arkansas, May 2, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Addresses - University Club of New York, January 30, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Addresses - University of Michigan Convocation on Population, November 15-17, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Addresses - University of North Carolina, October 19, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Addresses - University of North Carolina, October 19, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Addresses - Virginia League for Planned Parenthood, November 22, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Addresses - Young Men's Christian Association, April 11, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Addresses - West Virginia Wesleyan College, September 28, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Addresses - Whitney Museum, September 20, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Articles (A-M), 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Articles (A-M), 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Articles (N), 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Articles (N), 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Articles (O-Z), 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Articles - "American Art Review", June 1976 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Articles - "Family Weekly", 1974 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Articles - "Look", February 9, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Articles - "Look" - Background Material, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Articles - "Look" - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Articles - "Look" - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Articles - "Newsweek," (Bicentennial Article), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Articles - "Newsweek," (Abortion Article), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Articles - "New Yorker", November 4, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Articles - "Reader's Digest", December 1969 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Articles - "Reader's Digest", October 1970 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Articles - "Saturday Review", December 14, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Articles - "U.S. News World Report", April 8, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Autograph Requests, 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Automobiles, 1964, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - Awards, 1942-1969 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Awards, 1942-1969 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - Awards - Board of Trade, 1965 (Box P 171, Folder 13)
    - Awards - Japanese Embassy (Box P 171, Folder 14)
    - Awards - Parents' Magazine, 1967 (Box P 171, Folder 15)
    - Awards - RPSA recipients (Box P 171, Folder 16)
  - Awards, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Awards - American Medical Association, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - Awards - American Symphony Orchestra League, June 1963 (Box 16, Folder 148)
  - Awards - Concert Artists Guild, Inc., April 8, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (A-B), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (C-D), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (E-H), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (I-M), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (N-P), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award (R-Z), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award - Clippings, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award - Committee, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award - Preparation Manual, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - Awards - Protestant Council of the City of New York, Society for the Family of Man Award - Preparation Manual, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - Awards - (Margaret) Sanger Award, October 19, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Awards - Woodrow Wilson Award, February 23-24, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Bicentennial - General (A-C), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 163)
  - Bicentennial - General (D-H), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 164)
  - Bicentennial - General (I-M), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Bicentennial - General (N-P), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Bicentennial - General (R), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - Bicentennial - General (S), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Bicentennial - General (T), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Bicentennial - General (U), 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - Bicentennial - General (W), 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - Bicentennial - General - Media Meetings, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - Bicentennial - General - Memos and Working Papers, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Bicentennial - General - Memos and Working Papers, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - Bicentennial - General - Memos and Working Papers, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - Bicentennial - General - Memos and Working Papers, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - Bicentennial - General - Memos and Working Papers, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - Bicentennial - General - Minutes, Citizen's Committee for the Bicentennial Era, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - Bicentennial - General - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 179)
  - Bicentennial - General - Participants and Prospective Participants, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 180)
  - Bicentennial - General - Participants and Prospective Participants, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 181)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (A-E), 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (F-M), 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (N-P), 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (R), 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (R), 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Bicentennial - General - Requests and Proposals (S-Z), 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 187)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - General, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - General, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 189)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era (A-Z), 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era (A-Z), 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Board of Directors, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Congressional Hearings, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 193)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Declaration Advertisements, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Declaration Signatories, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 195)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Declaration Signatories, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 196)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Finances, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 197)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Fund-raising, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 198)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - Minutes of Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - U.S. Government, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era - White House, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - Biographical Material, 1963-1976 (Box 23, Folder 202)
  - Biographical Material, 1963-1976 (Box 23, Folder 203)
  - Biographical Material, 1963-1976 (Box 23, Folder 204)
  - Biographical Material, 1963-1976 (Box 23, Folder 205)
  - Chronological File, June 1962-July 1962 (Box 23, Folder 206)
  - Chronological File, June 1962-July 1962 (Box 23, Folder 207)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - Chronological File, August 1962-February 1963 (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 215)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 216)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 217)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 218)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 219)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 220)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - Chronological File, March 1963-October 1963 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 224)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 225)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 226)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 227)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 228)
  - Chronological File, November 1963-May 1964 (Box 26, Folder 229)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 231)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 236)
  - Chronological File, June 1964-January 1965 (Box 27, Folder 237)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 238)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 239)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 240)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 241)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 242)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 243)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 244)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 245)
  - Chronological File, February 1965-September 1965 (Box 28, Folder 246)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 247)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 249)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 250)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 251)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 255)
  - Chronological File, October 1965-July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 257)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 258)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 259)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 260)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 261)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 262)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 263)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - Chronological File, August 1966-May 1967 (Box 30, Folder 266)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 267)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 268)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 269)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 270)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 274)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 275)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 276)
  - Chronological File, June 1967-March 1968 (Box 31, Folder 277)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 282)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 284)
  - Chronological File, April 1968-November 1968 (Box 32, Folder 285)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 286)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 287)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 288)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 289)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 291)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 292)
  - Chronological File, December 1968-July 1969 (Box 33, Folder 293)
  - Chronological File, August 1969-December 1969 (Box 34, Folder 294)
  - Chronological File, August 1969-December 1969 (Box 34, Folder 295)
  - Chronological File, August 1969-December 1969 (Box 34, Folder 296)
  - Chronological File, August 1969-December 1969 (Box 34, Folder 297)
  - Chronological File, August 1969-December 1969 (Box 34, Folder 298)
  - Civil Rights, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 299)
  - Contributions, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 300)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions (A-L), 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 301)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions (M-R), 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 302)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions (S-Y), 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 303)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions - Afghanistan, King of, September 1963 (Box 35, Folder 304)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions - Hirohito, Emperor of Japan, September-October 1975 (Box 35, Folder 305)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions - Rockefeller Family, June 1970 (Box 35, Folder 306)
  - Dinners, Luncheons, and Receptions - White House Fellows, October 1970 (Box 35, Folder 307)
  - Employees, 1965-1971 (Box 35, Folder 308)
  - Finances, 1962-1973 (Box 35, Folder 309)
  - Gandhi, Mrs. Feroze (Indira), 1966 (Box 35, Folder 310)
  - Gifts, 1965-1970 (Box 35, Folder 311)
  - Hughes, Emmet J., 1960-1963 (Box 35, Folder 312)
  - Invitations, 1969-1971, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 313)
  - Invitations, 1969-1971, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 314)
  - Invitations to Speak (A-B), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 315)
  - Invitations to Speak (C-D), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 316)
    - Draper - Population Crisis Committee (Box P 171, Folder 17)
  - Invitations to Speak (F-K), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 317)
  - Invitations to Speak (M), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 318)
  - Invitations to Speak (N), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 319)
  - Invitations to Speak (O-T), 1964-1972 (Box 36, Folder 320)
  - Invitations to Speak (U), 1964-1972 (Box 37, Folder 321)
  - Invitations to Speak (V-Z), 1964-1972 (Box 37, Folder 322)
  - Invitations to Speak (A-B), 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 323)
  - Invitations to Speak (C), 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 324)
  - Invitations to Speak (D-I), 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 325)
  - Invitations to Speak (J-M), 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 326)
  - Invitations to Speak (N-O), 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 327)
  - Invitations to Speak (P-T), 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 328)
  - Invitations to Speak (U-Z), 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 329)
  - Jewelers, 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 330)
  - Jury Duty (First Panel Sheriff's Jury), 1962-1976 (Box 38, Folder 331)
  - King Bhumibol of Thailand, 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 332)
    - King Bhumibol (Box P 171, Folder 18)
  - Personnel, 1962-1971 (Box 38, Folder 333)
  - Personnel - Lamontagne (Raymond) Successor (CLOSED FOLDER), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 334)
  - Photographs - Distribution and Orders, 1964-1971 (Box 38, Folder 335)
    - Photographs (Box P 171, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Requests for, 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 336)
  - Policy and Planning Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 337)
  - Politics, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 338)
  - Politics, 1972-1976 (Box 39, Folder 339)
  - Portrait, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 340)
  - Property, 1963-1977 (Box 39, Folder 341)
  - Property, 1963-1977 (Box 39, Folder 342)
  - Property - Bassett Hall, 1960-1971 (Box 39, Folder 343)
  - Property - Bassett Hall, 1960-1971 (Box 39, Folder 344)
    - Property - Bassett Hall (Box P 171, Folder 20)
  - Property - Fieldwood Farm, 1948, 1960-1971 (Box 39, Folder 345)
  - Property - Fieldwood Farm (A-K), 1963-1971 (Box 39, Folder 346)
  - Property - Fieldwood Farm (L-Y), 1963-1971 (Box 39, Folder 347)
  - Property - Fieldwood Farm, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 348)
  - Property - Fieldwood Farm - Guest House, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 349)
  - Property - North Haven, 1962-1971 (Box 40, Folder 350)
  - Property - North Haven - Beverage Property, 1963-1968 (Box 40, Folder 351)
  - Property - North Haven - Witherspoon (Don), 1962-1968 (Box 40, Folder 352)
  - Property - North Haven - Witherspoon (Don), 1962-1968 (Box 40, Folder 353)
  - Property - One Beekman Place, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 354)
  - Property - One Beekman Place, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 355)
  - Property - One Beekman Place, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 356)
  - Property - One Beekman Place, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 357)
  - Property - One Beekman Place - Employees (CLOSED FOLDER), 1962-1970 (Box 41, Folder 358)
  - Property - One Beekman Place - Finances, 1962-1972 (Box 41, Folder 359)
  - Public Relations - General, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 360)
  - Public Relations - Ruder and Finn, 1968-1970 (Box 42, Folder 361)
  - Public Relations - Ruder and Finn, 1968-1970 (Box 42, Folder 362)
  - Radio and Television (A-K), 1962-1971 (Box 42, Folder 363)
  - Radio and Television (L-T), 1962-1971 (Box 42, Folder 364)
  - Radio and Television (U-W), 1962-1971 (Box 42, Folder 365)
  - Radio and Television, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 366)
  - Statements - House Ways and Means Committee, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 367)
  - Statements - House Ways and Means Committee, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 368)
  - Statements (F-P), 1964-1974 (Box 43, Folder 369)
  - Statements (U), 1964-1974 (Box 43, Folder 370)
  - Statements (V-Y), 1964-1974 (Box 43, Folder 371)
  - Trips - General, 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 372)
    - Fort Carson, 1971 March 29 (Box P 171, Folder 21)
  - Trips - General - Background Material, 1954, 1962, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 373)
  - Trips - General - Itineraries, 1952-1970 (Box 43, Folder 374)
  - Trips - Asia, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 375)
  - Trips - Asia, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 376)
  - Trips - Asia, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 377)
  - Trips - Asia (A-Z), 1965 (Box 44, Folder 378)
  - Trips - Asia - Dinners and Luncheons, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 379)
  - Trips - Asia, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 380)
  - Trips - California, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 381)
  - Trips - Colombia, February 1964 (Box 44, Folder 382)
  - Trips - Indonesia and Thailand, November 1976 (Box 44, Folder 383)
  - Trips - Iran, Pakistan, and Sweden, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 384)
  - Trips - Japan, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 385)
    - Trips - Japan, 1970 (Box P 171, Folder 22)
  - Trips - Japan, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 386)
  - Trips - Japan, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 387)
  - Trips - Japan, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 388)
  - Trips - Japan, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 389)
  - Trips - Japan and Korea, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 390)
  - Trips - Latin America, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 391)
  - Trips - Latin America - Clippings, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 392)
  - Trips - Mexico, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 393)
  - Trips - Middle East, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 394)
  - Trips - Russia and Far East, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 395)
    - Trips - Russia and Far East, 1966 (Box P 171, Folder 23)
  - Trips - Southeast Asia, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 396)
  - Trips - United States (Southern States), 1969 (Box 46, Folder 397)
  - Trips - United States (Western States), 1970 (Box 46, Folder 398)
  - Trusts, 1964-1972 (Box 46, Folder 399)
  - Trusts, 1964-1972 (Box 46, Folder 400)
  - Van Slyck, Philip, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 401)
  - Works of Art (A-B), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 402)
  - Works of Art (C-E), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 403)
  - Works of Art (F-G), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 404)
  - Works of Art (H-J), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 405)
  - Works of Art (K), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 406)
  - Works of Art (L-M), 1962-1971 (Box 47, Folder 407)
  - Works of Art (N-Q), 1962-1971 (Box 48, Folder 408)